Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the courage
that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here,
where the conscious points our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles!
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile!
We know we'll get there, no regrets!
Every tear that we've cried only helps!
Our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life!
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
That thing?
Are you sure you want to bring it along?
Uh, so...
you don't think I'll need it?
Honestly, I'm not certain you'll be
able to use it where we're going.
It's up to you.
Do as you please.
Thanks for letting me bring it.
I just really like this thing.
Do you mourn them?
No, sir.
You don't have to put on
such a formal act, you know.
Express yourself,
but don't make the same
mistakes as those fools
who couldn't comprehend
the true power of God.
They took me too lightly and so
forfeited their lives in the process.
Their failure was that their
minds were not controlled by fear,
and so they were not
prepared for battle with me.
Do you understand?
Yes, I-I suppose so.
I can't let him on to my plan.
I have no choice but to
obey everything he says.
An opportunity for escape will
present itself at some point.
But until then...
What's this?
It's only natural for you to be skeptical
it's the only ship of
its kind in the world.
And it can only be controlled by me in other
words it's powered purely by lightning.
Is that even possible i assure you
it is possible i channel my abundant
energy through material that Can handle
the power and automatically transmit
it throughout the ship what material
could possibly Withstand that much
power that's
right the gold i've
harvested from this island works perfectly
And i'm sure it will
make many inhabitants of
this island happy to
see a flying ship before
their Demise the sight of this magnificent
ship in flight will be
the last thing they see.
A flying ship?
I don't believe it.
If it really flies, I might not
have a chance for escape after all.
Behold the Archmaxim.
With this ship, we will reach
the land that knows no boundary.
We will travel to the endless birth.
We're outside.
We finally escaped.
The ground is made of stone.
Where are we?
What's going on, Luffy?
Hey, wait up!
We'll see!
We're free!
We made it out!
Woo-hoo! Where are we?
What are these old buildings?
It looks like this could be the place
that huge golden bell is supposed to be.
What is this place?
Wait, could this be our homeland?
Where'd that big hole come from?
Wolf!
Wait, where are you going this time?
Wait for me!
Hey, Zoro!
What's wrong with you?
Come on, say something!
How could this have happened to you?
How could any of this have
happened with you here? Yay!
Nami!
It's Nami!
She's not here!
Wipe her!
Wipe her now!
Bazooka guy was really strong,
but even he fell in this fight.
Who could possibly have done all this?
It was Eniril!
She's the only one who could
do something like this.
Eneru, huh?
That god guy?
My mantra didn't work at all the
whole time we were in the snake.
So I don't know what happened here, but
I do know it was Eneru who did this.
Robin!
Our navigator.
She went with him.
Just hang in there. It'll be okay.
So you're saying Nami was taken
away from here by that god guy?
Where?
I don't know.
Listen carefully.
If we don't do something,
Skypiea, it'll disappear.
What?
It'll disappear?
My homeland will be completely gone?
Everything will fall.
He said this nation in
the sky was unnatural.
He said he'd send it
crashing to the ground.
Enoru is definitely going
after the Golden Bell.
He won't destroy this
place until he's found it.
Right.
And you have to stop him.
But you must hurry because
there isn't much time left.
You can't let Inneru find
that bell. Don't worry.
I know where they are.
There are only two voices
left on this island.
It has to be Nami and Inneru.
Issie.
I need you to take me to them right now.
There it is, Angel Island.
Everyone, Esau,
the arch-criminals Pagaya and his daughter
Conis, along with their accomplice,
the former god Gonfall,
are still on the loose.
Please be on your guard.
If anyone sees these fugitives, please
alert me, McKinley, immediately.
Again, report any news directly to me.
In the name of the great god Iteru,
we of the White Berets will defend the
security of Skypiea with our very lives.
House!
Captain, I have a report.
What's the matter now?
What?
You say that Paggia's daughter's
just been seen in a harbor.
The heretic has entered
through gate number one!
I don't get it.
Why'd she come back when
she knows she'll be caught?
Don't let her get away!
Capture her at all costs!
Come on, criminal!
Please make way!
Move it! Out of my way!
Captain!
Captain McKinley!
It's the criminal! Stay away!
Judgements will fall on her!
Look at all that gold!
Remember your girlfriend
from Angel Island?
I've been listening, and it sounds like
she's causing an uproar among the citizens.
Conis?
No way!
She's the criminal!
Should be waiting on the going
Mary right now there's a great
deal of noise outside at the moment but
no matter it's hardly worth mentioning
about this
mantra ability that all of you
seem to possess can you use it
to locate a specific individual
not usually most of us lack
that ability however I can I am
unique in addition to my mantra
abilities my lightning powers
allow me to pick up electrical
vibrations and overhear conversations
when I hear someone say something
shall we say out of line
I cast my judgment on them
the range of my hearing
extends over this entire
land so that's it it's a
suitable talent for a god
isn't it run as fast as you
can people of the sky This
is Skypiea's last dance.
A party of angels dancing in the sky.
You,
have you ever seen the look on a mortal's
face when he suddenly loses his footing?
He's out of his mind.
I have to get away from here or else.
No, even if I get away,
he'll destroy the Sky Island.
There's gotta be something
I can do, but what?
What? I...
Is there something wrong?
Who is that?
No.
It's nothing.
Please!
You must listen to me!
No! Get back! Stay away! Everyone!
You have to listen to me!
Please calm down!
We don't have time to waste!
Get away from us, criminal!
Leave this island, you pestilence! Yes!
You must leave now, or we'll all be
destroyed when the judgment strikes you down!
You heretic!
Don't come any closer.
This is a burn bazooka.
I'll use it.
Everyone you have to go
to cloud end at the edge
of the clouds right away
before it's too late.
We have to escape to the
blue sea this land is
about to be destroyed
there's no time to waste.
Use every ship you can
find and leave angel
island at once what
kind of lunacy is this!
Eneru's planning to destroy
this land and everyone on it!
If we don't evacuate
now, we're going to die!
Ha!
You're crazy!
What kind of trick is this?
Is this revenge?
That's nothing to be
joking about, you know!
You idiot!
Don't talk that way about Eneru!
Oh, sorry.
what what's she doing now arrest her sir
hear me i refuse to
accept that anaru is god
Father…
No!
She must be insane! No! No!
That's strange.
The judgment didn't come. But why not?
And after committing such sacrilege
against God, I don't understand.
Hey, what's going on?
It's because there's no longer any
point in taking one life alone.
Skypiea is doomed.
It's true.
A member of the Divine Squad
escaped from Upper Yard.
He risked his life to
deliver that message.
He died.
He died with my father when
Aniru cast judgment on them.
Did God do that?
But why?
I thought he was supposed
to take care of us.
What does that lady mean?
There's no time left.
We have to get to the edge
of the clouds at once.
To Cloud End!
Wait just a minute.
We can't do it.
We can't just up and go like that.
We were all born and
raised here in the sky.
We can't live anywhere else.
Yeah, she's right.
None of us have ever even
visited the Blue Sea before.
How would we be able to live there?
Besides...
Are you going to stay here,
doing nothing, waiting to die?
We've all known for the past six
years what kind of a man Eneru is.
Has he ever shown mercy, compassion?
If he says he's going to do
this, then you know he will!
Maybe it's not that bad!
Maybe a miracle will happen or something!
And our island will be spared!
Yeah, why not?
Maybe he'll change his mind.
Yeah, yeah, that could happen.
If we know anything about
Enaru, we know this.
He's always had the power to bring us to
despair, to make us suffer and break us.
I tell you, what happens now makes
our past suffering insignificant.
It's not going to do any good
sitting and waiting for a miracle.
It's time to face the fact that
as far as this land is concerned,
God has abandoned us
before we pray before we
close our eyes to what's
really happening here!
We have to do what we
can to save ourselves.
We can't survive by hiding
behind his victims any longer!
If we do nothing, no
matter who we try to blame,
We're all going to lose our
lives, and it'll be our fault!
Now if we want to live, we must leave.
Oh Miss, do you have any idea
what happened to the Divine Squad?
My husband is one of them and I
can't leave the island without him.
And my son's a member, is he okay?
I haven't seen him in six years.
Me too.
My only son is with him too.
I don't...
The Divine Squad may already be...
I'm sorry, I don't know.
What have they been doing all
this time on the Upper Yard?
Are they still there?
Can't you tell us anything?
Please, calm yourselves.
I assure you the White Berets
will look into this matter.
We will find your family members and
make sure they're escorted safely to you.
Now hurry!
You must escape!
But Captain! Move along!
Captain, why?
I can guess what will
happen to the Divine Squad.
Inneru is that kind of man.
I've always known that.
But right now,
our priority is to make sure the citizens
are evacuated as quickly as possible.
I won't let this end like Byrdka.
Byrdka?
It was Eneru's homeland, a sky
island far to the southeast of here.
I've been told it disappeared
without a trace some six years ago.
Wait, six years ago? That's right.
Eneru destroyed his own
homeland, and then came here.
Byrdka was home to many strong warriors,
but they were helpless before Eneru.
An invincible god.
I don't know, maybe he really is.
You might already know this,
but we White Berets
were once in the Divine
Squad pledged to the
service of Lord Gonval.
We thought if we pretended
to betray the Divine
Squad and swore our
allegiance to Lord Inneru,
we could stay on the island and find
some way to protect the citizens.
But now it's all too clear
that plan was a failure.
We tried to keep anyone from
provoking Enoru's anger.
We hoped that if no one
disobeyed him, they'd be safe.
What else could we do?
For nothing!
It wasn't for nothing.
After all this time, I finally understand.
Captain, can I count on
you to handle things here?
Yes, but where are you going? Tell me.
Well, you see, there are some
people who don't know how to escape.
Some friends of mine.
I have to go back.
Take care.
Of course, the Blue Sea Dwellers.
House!
House.
I won't be able to move them all at once.
We've at least got to
reach the upper level.
Somehow, we must escape.
Issie!
You're sure it's this way?
Yes, we're almost there!
I'm sure this is the right way! Good!
That's it, Luffy!
That hole near left,
over there! That's it!
And that's where we're going!
as i thought they weren't
among the five survivors
now where in the world
could they have been hiding
Could it be?
How aggravating!
There's nothing I hate more than
when my predictions turn out wrong.
Hey!
Are you the one they told him or who?
If you mess with friends of
mine, then you mess with me.
Those fools were your friends.
You stay right there!
I'm coming up to kick your ass!
Mind your tongue, mortal.
You're speaking to God.
What makes you God anyway?
He's deliberately picking
a fight with Inru.
Be careful, Luffy.
B-Wait, Luffy, watch out!
I can hear it now, the angels party.
The citizens must have
learned of Skypiea's fates.
I wonder how far they can run before
the ground gives out beneath them.
I said, what makes you God anyway?
You'll find out.
Ah I see you are no
ordinary human but you're
a mere paramecia type you can't beat me.
Nothing that lives can stand
against me that's why I am gone.
Luffy!
No!
I'm impressed that you
managed to dodge it.
Sixty million volts! He dodged it?
Charging!
One hundred million volts!
Body!
Of course if I thought
about it I would have
realized it sooner
lightning can't hurt Loopy.
He's made of rubber
I've had enough of you!
Stay calm!
Physical attacks still
can't affect my body!
He's just a helpless monkey
from the Blue Sea World!
His electrical powers
are completely useless!
Enteru must have never imagined there was
someone in the world who
is immune to lightning!
It's incredible, but it's true!
Luffy may be the only person in
the world who can battle Eneru!
They're natural enemies!